thankyou.com 2015-09-10

# Citi ThankYou® Rewards - Our Privacy Statement

Our goal is to maintain your trust and confidence when handling personal information about you.

## Citi ThankYou® Rewards Online Privacy Statement

This notice discloses the privacy procedures of www.thankyou.com. Please read this policy to understand how we will treat the personal information about you.

Our Online Privacy Statement describes how we may collect, use and share information you provide when you visit this website, receive our emails or interact with advertisements we have on third-party websites. Detailed Explanation

**What are Third-party Websites?**   
Sites that are not operated by Citi and are not subject to our Online Privacy Statement. We encourage you to read the privacy policies on these sites. 

We encourage you to read the privacy policies on those sites.

### 1\. What Information Do We Collect?

We collect two types of online information: non-personal and personal.

#### Non-Personal Information

When you visit our site, we collect the IP Address Detailed Explanation of the device you use to connect to the Internet. In addition, we gather information such as what browser and which version of it you're using, the type of operating system you have, and which site you came from or advertisement you viewed or clicked on. This information helps us provide an online experience that matches your device and to manage our online advertising.

When you browse our site or receive one of our emails, we and companies we work with use cookies Detailed Explanation and/or pixel tags Detailed Explanation to collect information and store your online preferences. Cookies are widely used and most browsers are set up to accept them automatically. If you would prefer, you can choose to not accept cookies.

It's important to note that cookies and pixel tags do not capture any information that can personally identify you. The information they gather helps us to improve your online experience and may include:

  * Your response to one of our emails
  * Time and duration of your visit to our site
  * Pages you viewed while on our site

We may also supplement the information we collect with information we receive from other companies. For example, we may use marketing segments Detailed Explanation developed by us or other companies to customize certain services to your local area and provide relevant offers tailored to you.

#### Personal Information

You can visit and browse this site to find out about our program, Sponsors and rewards without giving us any information about yourself. When you enroll in ThankYou Rewards and set up your user name and password, we collect personally identifiable information about you as follows:

  * **Setting Up Your Account:** In order to redeem your ThankYou Points for rewards, you must set up a user name and password, either online or by calling the ThankYou Service Center. This process requires certain personally identifiable information including: your name, postal address, email address, telephone number, and a unique individual password, which we can use to verify your identity. You may also choose to provide us with information about your interests and ThankYou reward preferences.
  * **Transactions & Activities:** If you set up a user name and password and redeem for rewards, we will collect information about your transactions with us. This information includes areas of the website that you visit, redemption history, account activity, and shipping and billing information. We may also receive information about you, such as your earning activity from ThankYou Sponsors.

ThankYou Members may review and change contact information such as address, phone and email information by signing on and updating their personal profile.

### 2\. How Do We Use the Information We Collect?

Citi uses the information we collect about and from you to manage our business and to offer an enhanced, personalized online experience on our site and third-party websites. Detailed Explanation

**What are Third-party Websites?**   
Sites that are not operated by Citi and are not subject to our Online Privacy Statement. We encourage you to read the privacy policies on these sites. 

The information we collect allows us to:

  * Recognize you when you return to our site so we can personalize your experience
  * Process applications and transactions
  * Respond to your requests
  * Provide you relevant product and service offers on our site and in other advertising

We may also use personal information we have about you such as your email or postal address to deliver advertising to you directly or on third party websites.

### 3\. How Do We Use Information from Our Advertisements on Other Websites?

Companies we work with Detailed Explanation place and track advertisements on third-party websites. Detailed Explanation

Like most advertisers, we place advertisements where we think they will be most relevant to customers. We place advertisements by developing and using our own marketing segments Detailed Explanation that may combine online and offline information about our current and prospective customers. In addition, we may use marketing segments provided by online publishers and network advertising companies.

Network advertising companies that provide these services have their own privacy policies and are not subject to our Online Privacy Statement. Many of these companies provide ways to avoid targeted advertising provided by, or thru, them.

### 4\. Can You Control Your Information That's Collected and Used Online?

It's important to note that the information we use about you helps us provide you with products, services and experiences that benefit you. You have the ability to control how your non-personal inf`ormation is collected and used online.

#### E-Mail

When you provide your email address, we will use it to send you general notices or important news about your account, request your feedback or opinions and provide updates on special deals and offers that might interest you.

We believe you should be able to choose what kinds of information you receive via email. If you do not want to receive marketing materials by email, just indicate your preference on the email profile for your account or the 'opt-out' link provided in our marketing emails. Please keep in mind that we will continue to notify you by email regarding your account.

#### Flash objects

We may use Flash objects (sometimes referred to as "Local Shared Objects") on certain of our Web sites. We may use Flash objects to help us recognize you and your computer when you return to our site. Additionally, Flash objects may be used to help us avoid fraud or security attempts directed at our sites. Also if we display pages running Adobe® Flash® content (animated content), we use Flash objects to determine your browser type and version of Adobe Flash in order for you to view the content. As with regular cookies, we never store personal information in these Flash object files unless encrypted. Deleting cookies does not delete Flash objects. You can learn more about Flash objects - including how to control and disable them - through the Adobe interface. If you choose to delete Flash objects from our Sites, then you may not be able to access and use all or part of the Site or benefit from the information and services offered.

#### Cookies

You can control whether to accept cookies Detailed Explanation or not.

If you decide to not accept cookies, some features and services on our site may not work properly because we may not be able to recognize and associate you with your ThankYou Account. In addition, the offers we provide when you visit us may not be as relevant to you or tailored to your interests.

If you would prefer not to accept cookies, you can:

  * Change your browser settings to notify you when you receive a cookie, which lets you choose whether or not to accept it
  * Set your browser to automatically not accept any cookies

If you prefer to not receive targeted advertising, you can opt out of some network advertising programs that use your information. To do so please visit the [NAI Opt-Out Page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). Please note that even if you choose to remove your information (opt out), you will still see advertisements while you're browsing online. However the advertisements you see may be less relevant to you and your interests.

Additionally, many network advertising programs allow you to view and manage the interest categories they have compiled from your online browsing activities. These interest categories help determine the types of targeted advertisements you may receive. The NAI Opt-Out Page provides a tool that identifies its member companies that have cookies on your browser and provides links to those companies.

The Digital Advertising Alliance's Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising govern certain online advertising and data collection practices. The principles facilitate transparency about online advertising practices and support consumer choice in managing behavioral advertising. We subscribe to these Principles. For more information about the Principles and the About Ads icon visit http://www.youradchoices.com/.

#### Do Not Track

Although, there is no standard for how Do Not Track consumer browser settings should work on commercial websites, the industry has self-regulatory initiatives designed to provide consumers a choice in the types of ads they may see online and to conveniently opt-out from online behavioral ads served by some or all of the companies participating in these programs. For more information see the "About Ads" or NAI links provided above. Many of Citi's advertising vendors and companies participate in these programs. Using the choice mechanisms these programs make available may help you see advertising that is relevant to you or help you avoid seeing interest based advertising generally.

### EXTERNAL LINKS

The ThankYou Rewards website may contain links to other websites. While we try to link only to websites that we believe share our respect for privacy, please be aware that ThankYou Rewards is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other websites. Websites that are accessible by hyperlinks from the ThankYou Rewards website may use cookies. We encourage you to read the privacy statements provided by other websites before you provide personally identifiable information to them.

## NOTICE OF CHANGES

From time to time, we may change this Privacy Policy. The effective date of this policy, as stated below, indicates the last time this policy was revised or materially changed. Checking the effective date below allows you to determine whether there have been changes since the last time you reviewed the policy.

### EFFECTIVE DATE

This policy was last modified June, 2014.

**What is an IP Address?**  
An Internet Protocol address is a unique number, assigned to a computer or device that connects to the Internet, that identifies that computer or device. 

**What is a cookie?**  
A cookie is a small text file that a web server may place on your computer when you visit a site. The file uniquely identifies a computer. Information stored in a cookie sent by Citi can only be read by Citi or companies we work with. 

**What are Marketing Segments?**   
A pixel tag is a transparent graphic image, sometimes called a web beacon or tracking beacon, placed on a web page or in an email, which indicates that a page or email has been viewed. In addition, a pixel tag may tell your browser to get content from another server. 

These are groups of unique individuals or users categorized using information such as behaviors, demographics, attitudes and/or geographic differences. 

Companies can create marketing segments by using technologies like IP addresses to compile, over time, aggregated, non-personal information about how consumers are using the Internet. They consider where users saw and/or clicked on content and advertisements, and use this information to make inferences and predictions about the users' characteristics, interests and preferences. This information does not identify you personally nor does it report on particular online activities or behaviors. 

**What are companies we work with?**  
These companies are any third-party agents that conduct business on behalf of Citi. The services they provide include, but are not limited to, communications (e.g., email), marketing, data processing, customer acquisition and servicing and advertisement management.

When we use other companies to provide services for us, we require them to protect the confidentiality of information they receive. 

**What are Third-party Websites?**  
Sites that are not operated by Citi and are not subject to our Online Privacy Statement. We encourage you to read the privacy policies on these sites. 

**What are Marketing Segments?**   
These are groups of unique individuals or users categorized using information such as behaviors, demographics, attitudes and/or geographic differences. 

Companies can create marketing segments by using technologies like IP addresses to compile, over time, aggregated, non-personal information about how consumers are using the Internet. They consider where users saw and/or clicked on content and advertisements, and use this information to make inferences and predictions about the users' characteristics, interests and preferences. This information does not identify you personally nor does it report on particular online activities or behaviors. 

**What is a cookie?**  
A cookie is a small text file that a web server may place on your computer when you visit a site. The file uniquely identifies a computer. Information stored in a cookie sent by Citi can only be read by Citi or companies we work with.
